NATALIA MALVICINO



GRAPHIC/WEB DESIGNER

INFORMATION



Retiro, C.A.B.A.



/Aafterlife17



aafterlife17.github.io

() +54 9 11 6365-4880

nataliamalvicino 🖂 natalia.malvicino@gmail.com

ABOUT ME



I consider myself a creative, determined and organized person, searching for new challenges and to broaden my knowledge.

I have more than a year's experience working as a Graphic and Web Designer, currently studying to become a Frontend Developer

SKILLS

TOOLS

Web Development

Graphic Design

Languages

HTML5	
CSS3	
JavaScript	
WordPress	

Advanced Advanced Intermediate Beginner

Illustrator Premiere Pro Adobe XD Photoshop After Effects

Advanced Advanced Intermediate Intermediate Intermediate English Advanced











Canva









GIT

Google **Fonts**

Figma

Font Awesome

Icon Scout Bootstrap

Adobe Plunker Color

Stack

Swiper

EDUCATION

Web Designer/ **UI Designer**

Humanities and Social Science

Educación IT Institute 2018-2020

Carlos Steeb Highschool 2008 - 2012

EXPERIENCE

Graphic/Web Designer

Colonia Express 2021 - Present

<u>Graphic Design - Marketing campaing build and launch: graphic design for social</u> media using Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop. Daily newsletter design (Icomm Software). Multimedia and video making for social media and TV using Adobe Premiere Pro and Adobe After Effects. Editorial design for digital and printed newspapers and magazines. Graphic design of banners and pop-ups for website. UX/UI Design: working alonside the Web Developer to optimize the usability of the website and ensure brand identity.

Web Designer

Freelance 2020 - 2021

Website development for multiple clients using HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript.

Graphic Designer

Tekno Homes S.A. 2017 - 2018

Web design, working alongside the developer, web tests. Arrangement of presentation folders, display plotters, banners, product sheets, advertising campaigns. Management of the company's social networks. Translations.

Graphic Designer

Punto & Papel 2016 - 2017

Daily usage of Adobe software to make prints, display plotters, personal business cards, wedding invitations, etc.